(Raj:)Boy, you cannot catch a break,
can you?
(Mrs Cooper:)-Here you go, Shelly.
-Thanks, Mom.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Mrs Cooper:)Hold your horses, young man.
Here in Texas, we pray before we eat.
Oh, Mom.
(Mrs Cooper:)This is not California,
land of the heathen.
Give me.
(Mrs Cooper:)By his hand we are all--
(Sheldon:)Fed.
(Mrs Cooper:)-Give us, Lord, our daily--
-Bread.
(Mrs Cooper:)-Please know that we are truly--
-Grateful.
(Mrs Cooper:)-For every cup and every--
-Plateful.
(Mrs Cooper:)Amen.
(Mrs Cooper:)Now, that wasn't so hard, was it?
(Sheldon:)My objection was based
on considerations other than difficulty.
(Mrs Cooper:)Whatever. Jesus still loves you.
(Sheldon:)Thank you for carving a smiley face
in my sandwich.